April 15th, three days since that morning
Pile
I should really take out the trash.
Mizuhara!
That startled me. Don't throw the
door open while I'm walking by.
Your very existence
is loud, isn't it?
G-Good morning!
Morning.
She's being kinda... distant?
A-Am I just imagining it? Either way...
I'll never get used to how cute she is!
Opened the door
to a drop-dead beauty
She's like an alternate dimension
in this run-down apartment complex.
Does she have no makeup
on? Are you kidding me?
Her skin looks
so smooth
If that's how she looks au naturel,
And so clear, too.
I might prefer this, actually.
it makes you doubt
the very purpose of makeup.
She's not exactly dressed to kill,
and yet look at this aura!
Is she really the same species as me?
I wanna look, but I gotta hold back!
What a
freaking pervert
I-I'm thinking I'll rent
you out again next week.
I found a good place in Ikebukuro.
Has good clams, apparently!
Oh?
Okay, something's off.
What about Ruka-chan?
Huh? Ruka-chan?
I mean, didn't she stay over the other night?
See you, Kazuya-kun! Thank you!
She heard all that!
Rent-a-Girlfriend
It means the two of you... Right?
"Birthday and Girlfriend"
N-Nothing happened, really.
She just stayed the night.
She came over saying she'd make me dinner...
And I had no idea there
was a typhoon coming.
Remember how it was raining cats and dogs?
While we were arguing,
the trains stopped running, too.
And I didn't have the heart
to throw her out by herself.
I gotta state my case... The truth,
the whole truth, and nothing but the truth!
Though, well, it's only natural that she'd
misunderstand, after what she heard.
Lies.
It's fine. You don't have to lie to me.
Sorry if I've made things awkward,
but you don't have to walk on eggshells.
I do have some understanding
of what boys are like.
No, wait!
I'm the one who told you to date her,
and Ruka-chan is cute. I don't blame you.
M-Mizu...
As a hired hand, I can't
tell you not to rent me out,
but you should really know
where to draw the line.
H-Hey, Mizuhara-san?!
S
L
A
M
No way... Are you kidding me?
Came back
with the trash
I tried so hard to hold back,
and she still thinks I did it!
What is this torture?!
I didn't sleep with Ruka-chan!
I kept it in my pants, honest!
After all,
I... love you!
I won't let you take these kids.
See you, Kazuya-kun! Thank you!
I won't let you take these kids!
I'll forever remember the
joy I felt last night!
Focus, focus!
Turn
Walk
What do I do about this?!
Ruka-chan did stay over,
She's got
the wrong idea...!!
and given how I've always acted,
nothing I say is convincing.
Should I rent her out next
week and try to explain then?
Feels like she won't even
hear me out unless I do.
Huh?
Wh... Wha?!
Her birthday's this week!
Mizuhara Chizuru
Birthday - April 19
A pure and refined
high-class girlfriend
Oh, man! I almost let it
pass without noticing.
I haven't repaid her for
the Christmas gift yet,
so I can't ignore this.
She's already in a bad mood over
this whole Ruka-chan thing.
I'd better do something
for her and clear the air.
But... what should I get her?
I have zero idea what to
get a girl for her birthday.
Birthday Presents for Girls
Top 5 Ranking
Necklace
Holiday
Watch
Ring
Bag
The number 1 present girls want...  a necklace.
Number 2... a holiday?!
Nope.
Too needy!!
Are these girls for real?!
She gave me a phone case, so something
priced similarly would be good.
But you can't really throw a stuffed
toy away, so it might be annoying.
They don't really
feel like "presents."
And daily-use items would be like, "What?"
Not too expensive, not too cheap,
not too casual, not too serious,
not too special, and not too commonplace?
Does such a thing exist?
The most complicated thing in the world
Mizuhara Memo
The most complicated thing
in the world is deciding what
to give someone you're in a
complicated relationship with!
is deciding what to give someone you're
in a complicated relationship with!
I'm checkmated!!
Man, I don't even know
what Mizuhara would want.
Oh, right!
I could ask her!
Accept the terms & conditions and book.
Booking complete.
m 0 0 l 50 0 l 50 150 l 0 150
April
19th
I gotta settle on a present
for Mizuhara today.
Remember me? It's Kinoshita.
Looking forward to our date.
Sumi-chan
I bet she can help.
Kazuya-kun!!! I'm so happy!
I can't wait for our date either!
Where shall we go?!
Can we meet up in
the same spot as last time?
Wow, she talks a lot over text, huh?
Still cute...
Pedestrians
and Bicycles
Only
Like hell you and I are the same!
You were great today, too.
You were the best actor on the stage!
So don't tell me you're gonna give up!
Why would I need your
help that badly, anyway?
You really need to take a long,
hard look at reality.
Well, we have plenty of time,
Booked
for
2 hours
so I can ask about Mizuhara
toward the end or something.
Besides, there's no way
I could ask Ruka-chan.
I'd be diving
right into hell...
I think Sumi-chan and Mizuhara are
friends, so she probably knows.
I seriously thought that typhoon would
rip my run-down building outta the ground!
Yo, check her out.
What a cutie!
Sumi-chan's frighteningly cute again.
Yeah, she's painfully shy,
but if you didn't know that, she'd just
look like a pure, well-mannered beauty.
She's basically a girl ripped
straight out of a fairy tale.
She nailed her outfit today, too.
While she mostly wears cutesy stuff,
it's not like she lacks sex appeal...
No, stop! You're debasing
this innocent girl again!
Shall we get going?
Yup.
Couple Mode
Next, hug her from behind.
And eyes on the camera!
H... Hug?!
Three... two...
4/19 Date
Damn, I look gross.
Eyes wide open,
skin glowing
And Sumi-chan looks no different at all.
Her face is so slender!
This is the difference
in potential between us.
Damn it! I wanna show her
off as my girlfriend!
Though she's
a rental...
Mizuhara probably wouldn't
like a stuffed toy too much.
She's too
down-to-earth
I wish they taught you how
to pick presents in college.
What's up, Sumi-chan? You want the hat?
Oh, for me?
Well? Do I look good?
Clap Clap
R-Really? Yay.
...l.
You look... cool.
For real?!
Whoa, it's just 500 yen! Guess I'll buy it!
So
cheap
Gimme the positive reinforcement! All of it!
I can feel it!
PUFF PUFF
Hehehe♥
My dried-up sense of self-esteem
Hup Hup
is being brought back to life
by cute little Sumi-chan!
I say this without a doubt:
this feels so good!
Patch
Almost terrifyingly so!
PUFF PUFF
The walls of my common sense
are starting to creak!
Smile Smile
I'm falling into
my old ways again...
But...
She's totally acting like a
real girlfriend right now.
Slowly but surely, she's making progress.
I gotta move forward, too.
Man, that hour just flew by.
Y'know, there was something
I wanted to ask you today.
Oh, you don't have to get
all serious about it.
You know today's Mizuhara's birthday, right?
She's always helping me out,
so I wanna give her something.
But I'm not good at this kinda thing.
I don't know what a good gift would be.
You and she seem to talk often,
so I figured you might know what she'd want.
Gloom
Fluster
A-Ah, it's fine! It's fine if you don't!
Huh?
What now!?
Tap Tap
She's typing it out?
Show
Three Kingdoms.
Chizuru-chan loves
the Three Kingdoms.
BAM
The Three Kingdoms?
Not very "birthday present"-like, though.
It's a little clichéd.
Teary
I'm sorry! Thanks!
That was super helpful!
There's that thousand-yard stare again!
Oh, flowers?
Flowers, huh?
These are for you. Happy birthday.
Lame!
Have you tried looking in the mirror?
Yeah, that's a nope from me.
It's so not me.
You're overthinking it!
I'd be happy!
Sorry, I'm a real fool, aren't I?
Who do I think I am?
I know Mizuhara's a popular girl.
She won't think anything
of a gift I give her.
But...
Still, I can't bring myself to
just pick something at random.
Wh-Whoa!
What's gotten into Sumi-chan
all of a sudden?!
fuu                                fuu
Rent-a-Girlfriend
Th-This is...
a department store?
Department store to department store?
Abnormal Situation in Play
What? What's going on?
Glance
Should I say something?
Like, "Sumi-chan, all we've done
is move department stores."
"It hasn't changed anything!"
Probably not
these things
Or is there something we can only buy here?
Ah!
Huh? Where are we going?
Oh, the elevators?
Huh? The roof?
Not the stores?
Is there something up there?
Punch Punch
Impossible to decipher
Okay, I don't get it.
Kick Kick
Guess I should just shut up and follow her.
She seems
super serious
Huh? What are those voices?
Kids?
S Seats on Sale
Those Rent-a-Fighters, that ragtag
group of heroes has come to Nerima!!
Ragtag Heroes
Rent-a-Fighters
Oh, hey!
Ragtag Heroes Rent-a-Fighters
Hero Show
A hero show? This takes me back!
Take this! Rent-a-Lock!
So?
What does this have to do with the present?
She looks super happy!
Wait, does she just like this stuff?
Not related to
my present thing?
Did she forget all about
helping with the present?
B
E
A
M
Oh, well. As long as she's having fun.
Huh... So this is how hero suits
are designed these days.
Man, how many years has it been
since I last saw one of these?
Hey, that Pink is pretty awesome.
She's got a great body, and she moves great.
Go, Rent-a-Pink!
Is it just me, or is she really standing out?
You okay, Pink?!
Yes.
I won't let you take these kids!
Huh?
What?!
Give it up and get lost!
That voice...
Ugh... Curses!
I-I knew it.
It's Mizuhara!
Rent-a-Fighter!
Ugh, my powers are...
Pink!
As a Rent-a-Fighter, I must defend the Earth!
I get it.
Sumi-chan brought me here thinking I might
get some kind of hint from watching this.
Mizuhara...
Kids! Cheer them on with all you've got!
It's not just the rental girlfriend gig.
She's taking these jobs, too.
Hang in there!
Don't lose!
She barely has any time,
but she's still here doing this.
Just how hard on herself is she?!
So I at least want my grandma
to see me performing on screen.
That's my dream.
Hang in there,
Mizuhara!
It's time to go, huh?
Rental time was
until 6 PM
Thanks for showing me that.
I'll take it into account and try one
more time to think of a gift to give her.
Show
Presents are
all about the sentiment
Tap
Awkward intervals
If you put your heart into it,
I'd be happy with anything you gave me
Sumi-chan...
Yeah, you're right.
I feel a lot more confident now!
I'm glad I rented you today.
Thanks, Sumi-chan.
Take care on your way back!
I'll go look for a present!
So don't tell me you're gonna give up!
Okay, time to start searching in the
cosmetics department on the first floor...
Wait.
Sumi-chan?
S-Sumi-chan...
Okay, I'm waiting! What's up?
Didn't think
this through
Uh... erm...
She's not saying a thing.
She stops me and gives
me the silent treatment?
But she's blushing up a storm.
She must be trying to say something.
D-Did you forget something?
Wait, was the payment short?
What is it, then?
Why this silence...
I wanna know, too...
Like, your birthday, Kazuya-kun.
Huh? My birthday?
It's June 1st, why?
An
inexplicable
gaze...
New event
Kazuya-kun's birthday
Event added to calendar
What got into Sumi-chan back there?
Got me all
worked up
Huh? What's with the ring, Yuuko?
B-day gift from my BF.
Sparkle
Sigh
Gloom
Man, what do I even get Mizuhara?
Pressing Issue
Neverending Issue
Something not too expensive, not too cheap,
not too casual, and not too serious?
Something Mizuhara would
like to receive from me?
The more I think about it,
the more I feel like it doesn't exist.
If you put your heart into it,
I'd be happy with anything you gave me.
"Heart," huh?
Welp, I just gotta tough this out!
I love you, Mizuhara!
No, I'm fine.
Just felt a little chill, is all.
You didn't have to call me
to tell me happy birthday.
Should you really be up and about, Grandma?
Dinner?
I'm worn out today. No appetite.
What can I do about it?
Anyway, I need to take a
shower, so I'm hanging up.
Yeah, thanks.
Shi-chan
Happy birthday!
Happy birthday! I wanna perform
with you again, Chi-chan!
Shake    Shake
Thanks! Same here!
Happy Birthday
Because you're always helping me out,
and also in return for the phone case.
Sheesh. I told him it was a token of apology.
I know you're working really
hard to be an actress.
I hear these things alleviate
fatigue, so I hope they help.
Box within
the box
Pickled plum? Why?
P.S. Nothing happened
with Ruka-chan, I swear!
A small part
of the letter,
but it has a
threatening aura
Sheesh, what an idiot.
So sour!
Guess I'll cook some rice.
Gah!
Wriggle Wriggle
Has Mizuhara looked at it yet?
Maybe pickled plums were the wrong choice!
Am I some kind of geezer?
But then, what was the right one?!
Time for Mizuhara Memo #2.
If you gift an accessory to someone
you're on complicated terms with,
it'll likely find itself on some auction
site before long, so be careful.
Then what even is a good gift?
It's always a good idea
to pick a safe option.
But that won't convey my feelings.
Mizuhara!
What I really wanted to give you as a present
was my lifelong buddy, my v—
Rent-a-Kick!
Anyway, next time on Rent-a-Girlfriend:
"Booze...
...and Girlfriend."
"Booze and Girlfriend"
Alcohol is for adults only!